<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UNSW LoL Society</title>
    <description>UNSW League of Legends Society</description>
    <link>https://unswlolsoc.com</link>
    <atom:link href="https://unswlolsoc.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>UNSW LoLSoc Rumble 2019: Players to Watch [Semifinals Edition]</title>
        <description>
          Players you should be keeping your eyes on for the rest of the playoffs! - 
          UNSW LoLSoc Rumble 2019 Players to Watch [Semi-Finals Edition] We concluded the Quarter-Finals this Saturday evening with some very fun games to spectate! A strong mix of controlled macro play, with sprinkles of relentless bloodbaths going back and forth, was a perfect recipe for what we love about Rumble. Here...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-06-23-unsw-lolsoc-rumble-2019-players-to-watch-semifinals-edition/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-06-23-unsw-lolsoc-rumble-2019-players-to-watch-semifinals-edition/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>League of Legends is Now in its Modernist Phase</title>
        <description>
          Riot Games is pushing League into a new paradigm of gameplay.  - 
          It is a universal rule that everything grows and evolves, and League of Legends is no exception to it. From its humble beginnings to 10 year-old birthday, League is nearly indistinguishable from its early days. For 9 years, it has grown larger and more complex through the addition of new...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-06-09-league-of-legends-is-now-in-its-modernist-phase/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-06-09-league-of-legends-is-now-in-its-modernist-phase/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yuumean She’s Not an Actual Champion? Why The Magical Cat is Sitting at 35% Win Rate.</title>
        <description>
          Why does Yuumi have the lowest starting winrate of all-time? - 
          Yuumi, The Magical Cat, was introduced recently with Patch 9.10. As with all new champions, she received considerable play throughout the elos in the hopes that she would be powerful. However, she has underwhelmed so far, sporting the lowest win rate in the game so far at around 35%, 10%...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-05-19-yuumean-she-s-not-an-actual-champion-why-the-magical-cat-is-sitting-at-35-win-rate/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-05-19-yuumean-she-s-not-an-actual-champion-why-the-magical-cat-is-sitting-at-35-win-rate/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meet MSI’s Contenders</title>
        <description>
          It’s a return of new and old champions. - 
          MSI is coming up and if you haven’t been keeping up with the regular season of your favourite regions, this is the place to be. 2019’s MSI Contenders are: 1. LCK’s (Korea’s) SK Telecom T1 (SKT T1) “If you do your best but still lose at MSI, what will you...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 05:14:18 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-29-meet-msi-s-contenders/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-29-meet-msi-s-contenders/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Non-Competitive League of Legends: League Culture, Rotations, and Experimentation</title>
        <description>
          How Riot manages to keep Summoners Rift Competitive alongside introducing fun game modes. - 
          League of Legends has served for many players as a medium of competition. However, outside the world of eSports and rank climb, a handful of non-competitive players have also found their place in League. With the main available game modes being Summoners’ Rift, All Random All Mid (ARAM), and Twisted...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 05:08:46 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-29-non-competitive-league-of-legends-league-culture-rotations-and-experimentation/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-29-non-competitive-league-of-legends-league-culture-rotations-and-experimentation/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Week 7 Lan Party </title>
        <description>
          Thanks everyone for coming! - 
          Thanks everyone for coming to our (annual/termly) LAN Party! We hope you all had a blast playing on non-toasters/potatoes and on non-triple digit ping. Congratulations to the following duos for their excellent synergy in the 2v2 Tournament: 1st: Andrew Lee/Kacy Huang 2nd: Evan Lee/James Siu 3rd: George Wu/Raist Jurado If...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 05:42:41 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-15-week-7-lan-party/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-15-week-7-lan-party/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why YOU Should Love League of Legends ESports</title>
        <description>
          Why you, the player, should watch League ESports! - 
          “Winning mid lane always depends on the jungler.” (Read more of Doinb’s interview during LPL Spring 2019 with Inven here: https://bit.ly/2Cun04k) Just one of the reasons why fans choose to follow League of Legends Esports is because of this. Not how Doinb always flames Tian, but how relatable Doinb is...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 04:56:13 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-15-why-you-should-love-league-of-legends-esports/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-15-why-you-should-love-league-of-legends-esports/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>[UNSW LoLSoc 2019] Newsletter - Trimester 1 Edition 3</title>
        <description>
          Hey everyone, glad to see you all back! 🎉 - 
          ~Trimester 1 is Reaching a Close~ Hey everyone, glad to see you all back! 🎉 How have we been? I’ve had the pleasure of spending this weekend ploughing through two assignments while watching LEC Semis/Finals, LCK Finals, and LCS Finals in between. Congrats to SKT T1 for regaining form and...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 03:52:01 +1000</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-15-unsw-lolsoc-2019-newsletter-trimester-1-edition-3/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-15-unsw-lolsoc-2019-newsletter-trimester-1-edition-3/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Champion Reveal: Kanye West, the Greatest of All Time</title>
        <description>
           - 
          He first dropped out of College. He then won the heart of an entire generation, while pushing the boundaries of hip-hop, jazz, electropop alongside unparalleled commercial success. In Swahili, ‘Kanye’ means ‘The Only One’. Mr. West is the chosen one - the God amongst men, and after conquering the music...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 01:22:08 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-01-champion-reveal-kanye-west-the-only-one/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-01-champion-reveal-kanye-west-the-only-one/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>[UNSW LoLSoc 2019] Newsletter - Trimester 1 Edition 2</title>
        <description>
          Hey everyone, welcome back to our second newsletter of the term!! 🎉🎉 - 
          ~Midsem Blues~   :( Hey everyone, welcome back to our second newsletter of the term!! 🎉🎉 I hope you’ve all been hitting the books 📚📚📚, because 😢 midsems 😢 are on the way! I believe ✨✨ in everyone single one of you, so be sure to get HDs 🎓 and do me proud 😄! I, on the other hand,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 01:05:22 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-01-unsw-lolsoc-2019-newsletter-trimester-1-edition-2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-04-01-unsw-lolsoc-2019-newsletter-trimester-1-edition-2/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Epic Guide: How to Climb in LoL!</title>
        <description>
          Get to Challenger with this Guide! - 
          Who am I? Hey there! I’m Adam “Bucklava” Felah, and I’m here to tell you how to get that rank you’ve always dreamed of! Why should you listen to me? Because I have been playing League Of Legends for longer than you! Steps to Climbing 1. Win More Games! The...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 23:59:47 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-epic-guide-how-to-climb-in-lol/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-epic-guide-how-to-climb-in-lol/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who is the Cutest Pro Player?</title>
        <description>
           - 
          After years of relentless surveying, over eight thousand people have kindly volunteered their opinions into this controversial topic. Absolutely no bias can possibly be found as we have thoroughly run over the numbers ensuring they haven’t been tampered. The nominees and the results are in! The burning question on everyone’s...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 23:43:17 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-who-is-the-cutest-pro-player/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-who-is-the-cutest-pro-player/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Legendary Skins: SoundCloud 9 (Minus 5)</title>
        <description>
          SoundCloud have helped develop four new legendary skins in collaboration with some of the premier creative forces in music. - 
          To celebrate SoundCloud’s multi-year partnership with Riot Games to globally sponsor League of Legends esports, SoundCloud have helped develop four new legendary skins in collaboration with some of the premier creative forces in music. EkKodak Black The Rift has a river wide and long enough for him to drive the...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 23:28:40 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-new-legendary-skins-soundcloud-9-minus-5/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-new-legendary-skins-soundcloud-9-minus-5/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Week 5 Trivia Night</title>
        <description>
           - 
          To everyone who attended our Trivia Night on Friday, thank you! We are so glad you came and enjoyed a fun night of trivia, challenges, art, and flaming your friends who got the wrong answer. Congratulations to Sean Slappers for coming first with a grand total of 108 points! In...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 18:51:41 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-week-5-trivia-night/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-week-5-trivia-night/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>[UNSW LoLSoc 2019] Newsletter - Trimester 1 Edition 1</title>
        <description>
          To everyone new this year, welcome to UNSW LoLSoc! To our veterans, welcome back! - 
          Welcome Everyone!!! To everyone new this year, welcome to UNSW LoLSoc! To our veterans, welcome back! What you’re reading is our fortnightly newsletter, where we recap everything LoLSoc which happened of late and give you a sneak peek on future events! I’m Kenzo - your Publications Director this year. I’ve...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 17:46:55 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-unsw-lolsoc-2019-newsletter-trimester-1-edition-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-unsw-lolsoc-2019-newsletter-trimester-1-edition-1/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Favourite One-trick and Why She’s Back in Pro Play: The Return of Riven</title>
        <description>
          Everyone's favourite 3.5% one-tricked Toplaner is finally dashing into competitive play... But why now? - 
          Throughout the years of League’s existence, Riven, the Exile, has proven to be one of the most consistently popular champions. Her design and flashy kit with high outplay and 1v9 potential has earned her a dedicated audience of players including multiple OTP streamers such as BoxBox and Adrian Riven. However,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 16:10:53 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-your-favourite-one-trick-and-why-she-s-back-in-pro-play-the-return-of-riven/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-your-favourite-one-trick-and-why-she-s-back-in-pro-play-the-return-of-riven/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>End of Year Newsletter 2018</title>
        <description>
          A trip down memory lane - 
          Hi everyone, on behalf of both the outgoing and current executive team, we would like to wish all UNSW LoLSoc members a happy new year! Thank you for being a part of our 2018 and creating amazing memories with us! NEEKO-suto! Let’s take a look at the snapshots of our...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-01-13-eoy-newsletter-v2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-01-13-eoy-newsletter-v2/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
