<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UNSW LoL Society</title>
    <description>UNSW League of Legends Society</description>
    <link>https://unswlolsoc.com</link>
    <atom:link href="https://unswlolsoc.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Epic Guide: How to Climb in LoL!</title>
        <description>
           - 
          Who am I? Hey there! I’m Adam “Bucklava” Felah, and I’m here to tell you how to get that rank you’ve always dreamed of! Why should you listen to me? Because I have been playing League Of Legends for longer than you! Steps to Climbing 1. Win More Games! The...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 23:59:47 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-epic-guide-how-to-climb-in-lol/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-epic-guide-how-to-climb-in-lol/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who is the Cutest Pro Player?</title>
        <description>
           - 
          After years of relentless surveying, over eight thousand people have kindly volunteered their opinions into this controversial topic. Absolutely no bias can possibly be found as we have thoroughly run over the numbers ensuring they haven’t been tampered. The nominees and the results are in! The burning question on everyone’s...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 23:43:17 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-who-is-the-cutest-pro-player/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-who-is-the-cutest-pro-player/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Legendary Skins: SoundCloud 9 (Minus 5)</title>
        <description>
          SoundCloud have helped develop four new legendary skins in collaboration with some of the premier creative forces in music. - 
          To celebrate SoundCloud’s multi-year partnership with Riot Games to globally sponsor League of Legends esports, SoundCloud have helped develop four new legendary skins in collaboration with some of the premier creative forces in music. EkKodak Black The Rift has a river wide and long enough for him to drive the...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 23:28:40 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-new-legendary-skins-soundcloud-9-minus-5/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-31-new-legendary-skins-soundcloud-9-minus-5/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Week 5 Trivia Night</title>
        <description>
           - 
          To everyone who attended our Trivia Night on Friday, thank you! We are so glad you came and enjoyed a fun night of trivia, challenges, art, and flaming your friends who got the wrong answer. Congratulations to Sean Slappers for coming first with a grand total of 108 points! In...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 18:51:41 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-week-5-trivia-night/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-week-5-trivia-night/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>[UNSW LoLSoc 2019] Newsletter - Trimester 1 Edition 1</title>
        <description>
          To everyone new this year, welcome to UNSW LoLSoc! To our veterans, welcome back! - 
          Welcome Everyone!! To everyone new this year, welcome to UNSW LoLSoc! To our veterans, welcome back! What you’re reading is our fortnightly newsletter, where we recap everything LoLSoc which happened of late and give you a sneak peek on future events! I’m Kenzo - your Publications Director this year. I’ve...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 17:46:55 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-unsw-lolsoc-2019-newsletter-trimester-1-edition-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-unsw-lolsoc-2019-newsletter-trimester-1-edition-1/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your Favourite One-trick and Why She’s Back in Pro Play: The Return of Riven</title>
        <description>
          Everyone's favourite 3.5% one-tricked Toplaner is finally dashing into competitive play... But why now? - 
          Throughout the years of League’s existence, Riven, the Exile, has proven to be one of the most consistently popular champions. Her design and flashy kit with high outplay and 1v9 potential has earned her a dedicated audience of players including multiple OTP streamers such as BoxBox and Adrian Riven. However,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 16:10:53 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-your-favourite-one-trick-and-why-she-s-back-in-pro-play-the-return-of-riven/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-03-17-your-favourite-one-trick-and-why-she-s-back-in-pro-play-the-return-of-riven/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>End of Year Newsletter 2018</title>
        <description>
          A trip down memory lane - 
          Hi everyone, on behalf of both the outgoing and current executive team, we would like to wish all UNSW LoLSoc members a happy new year! Thank you for being a part of our 2018 and creating amazing memories with us! NEEKO-suto! Let’s take a look at the snapshots of our...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
        <link>https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-01-13-eoy-newsletter-v2/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://unswlolsoc.com/2019-01-13-eoy-newsletter-v2/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
